[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 7 + 7 \u00d7 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "70",
      "options": [
        "70",
        "72",
        "75",
        "68"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 2 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "21",
      "options": [
        "26",
        "19",
        "21",
        "23"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 6 + 9 \u00d7 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "60",
      "options": [
        "62",
        "60",
        "58",
        "65"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 6 + 4 \u00d7 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "38",
      "options": [
        "38",
        "43",
        "36",
        "40"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 7 + 8 \u00d7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "39",
      "options": [
        "41",
        "39",
        "44",
        "37"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 18 + 9 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "63",
      "options": [
        "61",
        "65",
        "63",
        "68"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 2 \u00d7 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "20",
      "options": [
        "22",
        "20",
        "18",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 8 + 8 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "21",
        "16",
        "14",
        "18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 8 \u00d7 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "87",
      "options": [
        "87",
        "89",
        "92",
        "85"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 3 \u00d7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "16",
        "12",
        "19"
      ]
    }
]